[Music]
today
i felt the need to cultivate peace in
the best way i know how
by creating alongside nature and
practicing
slowness
[Music]
on an earth that grows lavender and
golden glows
where blue mountains rise above the
clouds i think that peace of mind is not
only achievable
but grows in abundance once we begin to
nourish it
[Music]
when some flower beds needed to be cut
back
i decided to make a flower crown
something about it stirs in my heart the
memory of a little girl
running through the woods with
dandelions stuck in her hair
i find nothing creates a sense of calm
more
than connecting with childhood memories
that you cherish
remembering that there was a time when
the world is full of nothing but hope
and possibilities and then
realizing that things can still be that
way
[Music]
my prayer for peace in mind i went to
the labyrinth beside my house
and took the walk of life
a labyrinth isn't a maze though it may
seem to be full of confusing twists and
turns
however the path will lead you to your
destination
as you walk you will realize that the
purpose of the labyrinth
isn't to confuse you but to offer a
meditation on life
a new perspective challenging you to see
beyond the next two steps
and recognize the beauty in the big
picture
it is a dry hot windy day
and i was having quite a hard time
staying cool so i kept myself busy by
recording
a little song for you guys it's one of
my favorite fiddle tunes
i'm not a professional fiddler but i am
very excited to share this song
even though i myself was aware of the
mistakes i made in the recording i
knew i had to take a step back and just
accept that
all i wanted to do was share something
that
means a lot to me and doing my best at
it
and i have to be at peace with whatever
my best is
i don't actually play fiddle that much
it's
something that i pick up now and then
when i feel the need to
be more grounded or connect with nature
since i like to go outside
and play to the skies and offer up my
music
in a place where i can be alone yet
sometimes i feel like i do have an
audience and that nature is appreciating
my
my mediocre efforts
[Music]
julie
you